[{"answer": " Joseph, can I ask you a question about universities in the U.S.", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Joseph, can I ask you a question about universities in the U.S.", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Since Ive only been here eight months, Im not sure about how things work.  Ca", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Sure, they can.  Why", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Since Ive only been here eight months, Im not sure about how things work.  Ca", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Well, Im thinking of transferring next year", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Sure, they can.  Why", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " You are?  Why?  Dont you like it here", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Well, Im thinking of transferring next year", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " I do like the school here; I just dont like my program.  Studying biology is not lik", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 24, "question": " You are?  Why?  Dont you like it here", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " So, you dont want to study it anymore?  You want to switch schools an", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 28, "question": " I do like the school here; I just dont like my program.  Studying biology is not lik", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 34, "question": " So, you dont want to study it anymore?  You want to switch schools an", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " What do you want to study then", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Yeah", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Architecture", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 36, "question": " What do you want to study then", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats a big change", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Architecture", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I know.  This school doesnt have an architecture program.  So, if I want to stud", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Wow!  Thats a big change", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " I see.  Man, Im going to miss you if you leave.  But, I understand why yo", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 40, "question": " I know.  This school doesnt have an architecture program.  So, if I want to stud", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Is transferring easy", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " I see.  Man, Im going to miss you if you leave.  But, I understand why yo", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Its pretty easy.  The first thing you have to do is apply to the new school an", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Is transferring easy", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Will the procedure be the same as when I applied here", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Its pretty easy.  The first thing you have to do is apply to the new school an", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Pretty much.  Youll just apply as a transfer student.  Thats the only difference", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Will the procedure be the same as when I applied here", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " And once I get accepted, I just start attending the new school and its a smoot", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Pretty much.  Youll just apply as a transfer student.  Thats the only difference", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Well, there are a few things to keep in mind", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 57, "question": " And once I get accepted, I just start attending the new school and its a smoot", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Like what", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Well, there are a few things to keep in mind", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " If you transfer, you might lose credits, and it might take you longer t", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Like what", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Why", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 63, "question": " If you transfer, you might lose credits, and it might take you longer t", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " When you transfer, some schools will accept some transfer credits.  Tha", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Why", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Oh, I see", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 69, "question": " When you transfer, some schools will accept some transfer credits.  Tha", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " But, most schools have a limit to how many credits you can transfer, and yo", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Oh, I see", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " How many credits can I transfer", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 74, "question": " But, most schools have a limit to how many credits you can transfer, and yo", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " It just depends on the school you go to.  Here its only six credits", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 78, "question": " How many credits can I transfer", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Oh, thats not a lot", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 79, "question": " It just depends on the school you go to.  Here its only six credits", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " I know.  Thats why it might delay your graduation.  You might have to repea", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Oh, thats not a lot", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Thats not good", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 84, "question": " I know.  Thats why it might delay your graduation.  You might have to repea", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " I know.  You know another thing to keep in mind is your status as a", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Thats not good", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Is transferring different for me", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I know.  You know another thing to keep in mind is your status as a", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " My friend from Korea transferred last year, and he said there were som", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Is transferring different for me", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " I guess I should talk to my ISA first before I do anything", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 95, "question": " My friend from Korea transferred last year, and he said there were som", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " I would.  Anyways, thats all I know about transferring.  Ill rack my brain ", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 96, "question": " I guess I should talk to my ISA first before I do anything", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " OK, thanks!  Ill look on our schools website about it too", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 100, "question": " I would.  Anyways, thats all I know about transferring.  Ill rack my brain ", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " Good idea", "docId": "06-09", "aSentId": 101, "question": " OK, thanks!  Ill look on our schools website about it too", "qSentId": 100}]
